

Martin Šuba JavaScript developer

### **About**

Software engineer developing applications in JavaScript/TypeScript focused on web technologies. Specializes in front-end part of applications and websites. Has experience with many aspects of web development such as working with front-end frameworks, Node.js, REST API, developing browser extensions, writing unit tests, refactoring and building responsive and pixel perfect websites.

# **Experience**

## JavaScript developer

#### **SaferPass**

October 2017 - Present Bratislava, Slovakia

Taking care of front-end part of SaferPass password manager browser extension. Mostly working with JavaScript/TypeScript, AngularJS, web extension API, web API, Node.js. Implementing new features as well as refactoring legacy code and writing unit tests.

## Front-end web developer

#### **WEZEO**

September 2015 - September 2017 Bratislava, Slovakia

Building front-end of responsive cross-browser/platform web and mobile applications. Working mostly with HTML, SASS, JavaScript, jQuery and frameworks like AngularJS, Angular and Ionic.

### Front-end web developer

#### **Elite Solutions**

April 2014 - August 2015 Bratislava, Slovakia

Creating web sites and user interfaces using HTML, CSS and JavaScript. Cooperating with graphic designers and back-end developers. Working for clients like O2, Sberbank, SLSP, VÚB and Hyundai.

## Front-end web developer

#### pelicantravel.com

April 2013 - March 2014 Bratislava, Slovakia

I focused mainly on coding web pages, coding e-mail newsletters, customizing WordPress templates and some other online marketing activities.

#### Front-end coder

#### webikon

November 2012 - March 2013 Bratislava, Slovakia

WordPress themes coding (HTML + CSS + jQuery)

# **Education**

### **University of Economics in Bratislava**

#### Management

2013 - 2015

Master's degree

## University of Economics in Bratislava

**Business Economics and Management** 

2010 - 2013

Bachelor's degree

## **Skills**

### development:

Js JavaScript

Angular

■ MochaSASS

TypeScript

GitJasmine

Node.js

WebpackTravis

React / Redux

m npm

Ohrome Extensions

# language:

English Czech Slovak

### other: